{"page":"1","rows":[{"code":"5328","codename":"5328-云南省_西双版纳傣族自治�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"云南省_西双版纳傣族自治�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"5328"},{"code":"5329","codename":"5329-云南省_大理白族自治�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"云南省_大理白族自治�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"5329"},{"code":"5331","codename":"5331-云南省_德宏傣族景颇族自治州","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"云南省_德宏傣族景颇族自治州","rowversion":"1","urid":"5331"},{"code":"5333","codename":"5333-云南省_怒江傈僳族自治州","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"云南省_怒江傈僳族自治州","rowversion":"1","urid":"5333"},{"code":"5334","codename":"5334-云南省_迪庆藏族自治�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"云南省_迪庆藏族自治�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"5334"},{"code":"5401","codename":"5401-西藏自治区_拉萨�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_拉萨�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"5401"},{"code":"5421","codename":"5421-西藏自治区_昌都地区","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_昌都地区","rowversion":"1","urid":"5421"},{"code":"5422","codename":"5422-西藏自治区_山南地区","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_山南地区","rowversion":"1","urid":"5422"},{"code":"5423","codename":"5423-西藏自治区_日喀则地�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_日喀则地�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"5423"},{"code":"5424","codename":"5424-西藏自治区_那曲地区","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_那曲地区","rowversion":"1","urid":"5424"},{"code":"5425","codename":"5425-西藏自治区_阿里地区","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_阿里地区","rowversion":"1","urid":"5425"},{"code":"5426","codename":"5426-西藏自治区_林芝地区","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"西藏自治区_林芝地区","rowversion":"1","urid":"5426"},{"code":"6101","codename":"6101-陕西省_西安�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_西安�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6101"},{"code":"6102","codename":"6102-陕西省_铜川�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_铜川�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6102"},{"code":"6103","codename":"6103-陕西省_宝鸡�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_宝鸡�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6103"},{"code":"6104","codename":"6104-陕西省_咸阳�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_咸阳�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6104"},{"code":"6105","codename":"6105-陕西省_渭南�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_渭南�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6105"},{"code":"6106","codename":"6106-陕西省_延安�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_延安�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6106"},{"code":"6107","codename":"6107-陕西省_汉中�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_汉中�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6107"},{"code":"6108","codename":"6108-陕西省_榆林�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_榆林�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6108"},{"code":"6109","codename":"6109-陕西省_安康�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_安康�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6109"},{"code":"6110","codename":"6110-陕西省_商洛�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"陕西省_商洛�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6110"},{"code":"6201","codename":"6201-甘肃省_兰州�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"甘肃省_兰州�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"6201"},{"code":"6202","codename":"6202-甘肃省_嘉峪关市","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"甘肃省_嘉峪关市","rowversion":"1","urid":"6202"},{"code":"4116","codename":"4116-河南省_周口�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"河南省_周口�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4116"},{"code":"4117","codename":"4117-河南省_驻马店市","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"河南省_驻马店市","rowversion":"1","urid":"4117"},{"code":"4201","codename":"4201-湖北省_武汉�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_武汉�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4201"},{"code":"4202","codename":"4202-湖北省_黄石�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_黄石�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4202"},{"code":"4203","codename":"4203-湖北省_十堰�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_十堰�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4203"},{"code":"4205","codename":"4205-湖北省_宜昌�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_宜昌�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4205"},{"code":"4206","codename":"4206-湖北省_襄樊�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_襄樊�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4206"},{"code":"4207","codename":"4207-湖北省_鄂州�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_鄂州�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4207"},{"code":"4208","codename":"4208-湖北省_荆门�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_荆门�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4208"},{"code":"4209","codename":"4209-湖北省_孝感�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_孝感�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4209"},{"code":"4210","codename":"4210-湖北省_荆州�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_荆州�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4210"},{"code":"4211","codename":"4211-湖北省_黄冈�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_黄冈�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4211"},{"code":"4212","codename":"4212-湖北省_咸宁�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_咸宁�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4212"},{"code":"4213","codename":"4213-湖北省_随州�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_随州�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4213"},{"code":"4228","codename":"4228-湖北省_恩施土家族苗族自治州","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_恩施土家族苗族自治州","rowversion":"1","urid":"4228"},{"code":"4229","codename":"4229-湖北省_三峡","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_三峡","rowversion":"1","urid":"4229"},{"code":"4290","codename":"4290-湖北省_省直辖行政单�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖北省_省直辖行政单�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4290"},{"code":"4301","codename":"4301-湖南省_长沙�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_长沙�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4301"},{"code":"4302","codename":"4302-湖南省_株洲�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_株洲�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4302"},{"code":"4303","codename":"4303-湖南省_湘潭�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_湘潭�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4303"},{"code":"4304","codename":"4304-湖南省_衡阳�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_衡阳�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4304"},{"code":"4305","codename":"4305-湖南省_邵阳�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_邵阳�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4305"},{"code":"4306","codename":"4306-湖南省_岳阳�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_岳阳�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4306"},{"code":"4307","codename":"4307-湖南省_常德�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_常德�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4307"},{"code":"4308","codename":"4308-湖南省_张家界市","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_张家界市","rowversion":"1","urid":"4308"},{"code":"4309","codename":"4309-湖南省_益阳�?","createdby":"admin","createdon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","dataRight":"1111110","datarightflag_system":"1111110","description":"","isactive":"�?","lastmodifiedby":"admin","lastmodifiedon":"2016-04-05 08:00:00","name":"湖南省_益阳�?","rowversion":"1","urid":"4309"}],"total":361,"totalpage":8}